<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ericka Salas</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ericka Salas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Data Science Journey</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/04/my-data-science-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/04/my-data-science-journey/</guid>
      <description>My freshmen year at UT Austin I was unsure in the career I wanted to pursue. I started as a Public Health major and was on the Pre-Med track. It was the only career track I had interest at the time. It was until I became involved in the Freshmen Research Initiative program that made me realize what I wanted to pursue.
 Spring 2019 I was in the Big Data in Biology cohort and became exposed to Python and RNA-seq data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Data Wrangling and Data Exploration Broadway Data Analysis Project by: Ericka Salas (efs554)
 Introduction of Broadway Data Before the COVID-19 pandemic hit, I worked at a box office on UT Austin&#39;s campus that mainly sold tickets to concerts and broadway performances. I became a huge broadway fan and for the past two years of working in the office, attending broadway musicals has always been fun and exciting. I miss the feeling of the lights dimming at the beginning of a show or intermission conversations on the songs I enjoyed the most.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Modeling, Testing, and Predicting Analysis of Attitude Towards Science Survey Project by: Ericka Salas (efs554)
 Introducing Dataset - Science Study! Growing up I loved science and I continue to do so. Though, how do other people feel about science based on different factors? The dataset that I am analyzing is a school science survey dataset that is based on the attitudes to science based on sex, private or public school, and class in two different Australian states.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
